Ash Murphy

UI/UX Designer



ash-murphy-ui-ux.github.io



ash.murphy.uiux@gmail.com



0466285975

Summary

I'm a graduate from Deakin Burwood campus with two internships behind me and I'm hungry for more. I excel in fast paced environments both on a team and working solo.

I am working to become a professional User Interface and User Experience designer and look forward to the challenges and experiences of working in the industry.

Software

- Adobe XD
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe InDesign
- Adobe Photoshop
- Sketch
- Figma
- Invision

Skills

- User Interface design
- User Experience design
- Interaction design
- UI Graphic design
- Wireframing
- Interactive prototyping
- Usability Testing
- UX Writing
- HTML/CSS/JS

Talents

- Strong interpersonal skills developed over years of retail work
- Experience with leading and working teams in various university projects.
- Working autonomously or collaborating with others.
- Highly developed organisational skills and competent in managing my own time.



Education

Deakin University Bachelor of Information Technology (Interactive Media)

2019, Burwood

Experience

Darkspede - UI Design

Jul 2017 - Feb 2018, North Melbourne

As part of the capstone program at Deakin University I was given the opportunity to work with Darkspede, a VR company based in North Melbourne. As a team of 5, then later 7, we designed and built a prototype smart home app to Darkspede's specifications. I oversaw the design of the user interface and I assisted with many aspects of user experience within the app.

This experience with Darkspede taught me about building relationships and working with a client. I also greatly improved my skills working within a team instead of solo and I was able to get plenty of design and workflow tips from my team members.

Energy Umpire - UI/UX Design

Nov 2018 - Feb 2019, Melbourne Docklands

For my IT internship at Deakin, I joined Energy Umpire, a start-up energy comparison service based in Docklands. I was tasked with redesigning their website, EDM, and onboarding form.

As a start-up, Energy Umpire is only a small team and they were eager to have me working with them. I mostly went back and forth between the main designer and the CEO, creating and refining my designs using Adobe XD, Illustrator and Invision until we were all satisfied with the result. I assisted their developer with implementing the website designs on Wordpress with some custom HTML.

For their new emails, I was responsible for both the UX copy and graphic design, creating designs for advertising as well as customer retention.

Ritchies IGA - Retail Floor Assistant

Oct 2013 - Ongoing, Dromana

I have worked at Ritchies for over 7 years now as a floor assistant, which mainly involves stocking shelves and assisting shoppers. My time at Ritchies has greatly boosted my confidence in speaking and working as a team with others, as well as my everyday problem solving skills. I have been offered a manager position on two occasions, but I turned them down in order to focus on my studies.

References

 Susan Dvorak - Ritchies Dromana Dairy Manager Personal Ph: 0448252616 Work Ph: 59872766

 Alan Rattray - Energy Umpire Founder Ph: 0418190783